Guide to the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America records, 1914-1980.
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America records, 1914-1980.
- II. Joseph Schlossberg correspondence, 1914-1929. (Box 8-17)
  - Garfield, Nathan (Jewish Branch of the Socialist Party) 1918 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Gegretario, G.M. (Philadelphia Joint Board) 1925 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Gelfand, M. (Local 207, Woodbine, N.J.) 1918 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - General Executive Board, 1915 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Genis, Sander (Manager, Twin City Joint Board) 1920 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Gerber, Julius (Socialist Party, N.Y.) 1914 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Gertler, Morris (Toronto Joint Board) 1916-17 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Gilles, S. (Coat Makers Local, Local 140, of Philadelphia) 1914-17, Organizing Philadelphia; request for a "sick benefit system". (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Ginther, S. (United Tailors of Cleveland) 1918 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Gitchell, B.H. (American Men's and Boy's Clothing Manufacturers Assoc.) 1919 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Glickman, B. (telegram) 1919 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Gliebter, P. (Women's Circle) 1925 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Gold, Joseph (Children's Clothing Workers Joint Board) 1923, Report on racketeering charges against Max Gimber (Secretary, Children's Clothing Workers Joint Board). (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Goldblatt, Selma (Secretary, Local 235, Rochester) 1914-15, Question of amalgamation with the Tailors' Industrial Union (formerly the Journeymen Tailors' Union); Gompers sides with Rickert faction; Rochester press; organizing Italian, Polish and German workers. (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Goldmacher, M. (Non-Basted Children's and Sailor Jacket Makers Union) 1917 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Goldstein, David (Business Agent, Local 36, Baltimore) 1914-20 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Goldstein, I. (District Council No. 2, Philadelphia) 1916-17, Reports on the strike at Kirschbaum's. (Box 10, Folder 48a)
  - Goldstein, Michael (Secretary, Joint Board of the Shirt and Boys' Waist Makers Union) 1920 (Box 10, Folder 48b)
  - Gordon (Lynn Custom Tailors, Lynn, Mass.) 1920 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Gould, Samuel (Pants Makers Union, Worcester, Mass.) 1918 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Grandinetti, Emilio (Organizer, Chicago) 1916, Discussion of Philadelphia organizing drives in 1913 and relations between Italian and Jewish workers. (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Greco, Andrew (Organizer, Springfield, Mass.) 1920 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Greenberg, Abraham (Custom Pants Makers Union of Philadelphia) 1916-20, Concern over organizing the New York Custom Tailors; complaints against Mr. Chas. Bornstein (Business Agent for Custom Pants Makers). (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Gribow, William (Chicago Joint Board) 1919 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Groat, George (University of Vermont) 1916, Criticisms of Groat's A Study of Organized Labor In America. (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Gruman, A. (Joint Board of Montreal) 1917 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Hammond, Fred (Assemblyman, N.Y.S.) 1920 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Hayes, John J. (Cutters Union, Boston) 1918 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Held, William (American Federation of Full Fashioned Hosiery Workers) 1917 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Herwitz, H.K., 1924 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Hillman, Sidney, 1914-15, Substantial correspondence documenting the Chicago strike. Includes accounts of police brutality, public support for strikers and the appearance of Mother Jones. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Hillman, Sidney, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Hillman, Sidney, 1917-24 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Hoffman, Max (Brotherhood of Tailors) 1917, Organizing Rochester, N.Y. tailors. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Hollander, Louis (Uniform Dept.) 1914-19 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Holtzman, David (Coat Pressers, Philadelphia) n.d. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Horowitz, Charles (Montreal, Canada) 1914 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Horowitz, H. (United Tailors of Columbus, Ohio) 1917 (Box 11, Folder 11a)
  - Hsia, Pinfang (Harvard student) 1925, Chinese Students' Monthly. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Hudinski, Adam (Local 151, Milwaukee) 1917 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Hunt, E.E. 1919, Philadelphia newspaper refuses to print ACWA advertisement relating to the A & B Kirschbaum & Co. strike. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Huster, E. (Secretary, Local 150-A, Boston) 1916, Huster resigns from his position as Secretary of Local 150-A. (18pp) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Hyde, Charles (Brotherhood of Metal Workers) 1915, Statement of support for the ACWA and opposition to the UGW. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - International Clothing Workers Federation (Amsterdam, Holland) 1921-25, English translation of German text inaccurate in regard to discussion of emigration. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Istzkowitz, S. (Local 207, Woodbine, N.J.) 1918 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Jacobs, S.W. (Lawyer, Montreal Clothing Manufacturers Association) 1917, Correspondence concerning arbitration between the Montreal Clothing Manufacturers Association and the ACWA. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Jani, J. (Chicago Joint Board) 1916 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Jenkins, A. (Boston Joint Board) 1925 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Johannsen, A. (Chicago Joint Board) 1919-20 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Jurgelionis, Kleofas, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Kadish, Gertrude (Buffalo Joint Board) 1919 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Kadsel, A. (Secretary, Local 269, Chicago) 1925 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Kallen, Horace, 1923, Charges against M. Gimber (see also box 10, file folder 45, Gold, Joseph). (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Kaminsky, Joseph (Chicago Joint Board) 1918 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Kantorwitz, I. (Children's Jacket Makers Union) 1914-17 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Kaplan, Helen (Chicago clothing worker) 1925 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Karp, Daniel (Local 207, Vineland, N.J.) 1917, Organizing Italian and Jewish workers; strike. (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Katz, J. (Philadelphia clothing worker) 1918 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Kaufman, May (Organizer, Rochester) 1917 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Kellner, J. (Local 86, Pittsburgh) 1918-20 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Keof, Arthur (Railroad telegrapher) 1925 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Klein, Nicholas (ACWA attorney, Cincinnati) 1914-19, Significant account of events leading to the tailors' victory at H. Sonneborn & Co.; Locals 113 and 121 vs. John Riesenberg;question of "non-Jewish nationalities replacing Jews in the tailoring industry." (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Kleinman, Nicholas (Business Agent, Local 24, N.Y.C.) 1917-18, Detailed account of cutters' and tailors' strike in Red Bank, N.J.(8pp); child labor at Penn Clothing Co. (West Reading, Pa). (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Kline, L. (Lynn, Mass. Custom Tailors) (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Kopald, Louis (Beth Zion Temple, Buffalo, N.Y.) 1919 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Kowski, Les (Rochester Joint Board) 1923 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Krammer, Samuel (Local 39, Chicago) 1925 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Krause, Harry (Examiners' and Bushelmen's Union of Baltimore) 1919 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Krechowsky, David (Local 220, New Haven) 1914-15 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Kreman, B. (Local 153, Philadelphia) 1918 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Kroll, Jack (Organizer, Chicago, Cincinnati, Louisville) 1919-25 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Krzycki, Leo (Organizer, St. Louis, Buffalo) 1925, "local liberals" support St. Louis strikers; worker arrests; violence toward women strikers. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Kurtz, Joseph (Boston clothing worker) 1918 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Kwitny, Benjamin (Business Agent, Local 145, Indianapolis, Indiana) 1918-19 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - LaGuardia, Fiorello 1917-19, Conscription; freedom of speech and the press; the Reinstein case; "the Mongolia affair;" H.R. 98., statement on the terms of peace to be made with Germany, introduced by Representative Sweet; LaGuardia's decision to render active military service; Max Duberman's release from the Navy; repression of the civil liberties of discharged sailors and soldiers who are union members and exercise their right to picket, and The Advance "held up by the post office;" Utica police force Hillman and organizers out of the city. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Landfield, A. (Joint Board of Boston) 1918 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Lavique, Louis (Baltimore Clothing Cutters) 1919 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Lazaroff, B.A. (Local 220, New Haven) 1916 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Levin, Joseph (Baltimore Coat Makers Union) 1914 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Levin, Sam (Organizer, Chicago, Louisville and St. Louis) 1914-25, The arrest of Ed Anderson; "the Louisville situation." (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Levine, Joseph (Secretary-Treasurer, Boston Joint Board) 1917, Levine's attack on Potofsky. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Licastro, Phillip (Rochester Joint Board) 1925 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Lifshitz, Isidor (Business Agent, Local 174, Worcester, Mass.) 1918-20 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Lincors, Anna (Organizer, St. Louis) 1916 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Lindsay, Miss (Organizer, Buffalo) 1923 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Locals, general notices to, 1915-28, Discussion of women as "real live members not merely dues payers;" the true mission of labor unions; securing citizenship; the People's Council of America for Democracy and Peace; soldiers picketing. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Loenthall, Max (Jewish Daily Forward) 1914 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Lohse, Dora (Shirt Makers Union, Local 153, Philadelphia) 1918, Lohse's resignation. (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Lojis, Ignatius, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Lomonossoff, Raissa (Chicago Joint Board) 1920, Discussion of the need for a women's local. (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - London, Meyer (Socialist Congressman) 1914 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Longuet, Jean (Le Populaire de Paris) 1923, "strike of the clothing girl workers, the 'midinettes' as they are called here." (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Lowenthal, Szold and Perkins (ACWA attorneys) 1923-25, lawyers' fees. (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Lucia, Carmen (Rochester Joint Board) 1925 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - MacIlwain, George (Babson's Statistical Organization Reports on Fundamental Business Conditions For Merchants, Bankers and Investors) 1920 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - MacKinnon, F.A. (Lynn Custom Tailors) 1918-20 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Mackline, Charles (Baltimore) 1918 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Madanick, Harry (Organizer, Baltimore) 1915, Reference to Mr. H. Goldstein (of North Carolina) wanting to unionize the "5 hands" he employs;" Chicago work being made in Baltimore. (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Madanick, Harry (Organizer, Baltimore & Montreal) 1916, Baltimore: Strike at L. Greif & Bros.; fighting with the I.W.W.; Montreal: organizing French, Italian and Jewish workers; victories at H. Kellert & Sons and Freedman Co. (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Madanick, Harry (Organizer, Montreal and Toronto) 1917, The Grafton shop strike in Dundas; description of the Nov. 1917 American Federation of Labor Convention, particularly a discussion which ensued over a resolution, presented by the Journeymen Tailors Union, which called for the establishment of a Needle Department. (Box 12, Folder 34-35)
  - Madanick, Harry (Organizer, Montreal and Toronto) 1918 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Magnes, J.L. (Sonneborn mediator) 1914-16 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Maisch, John (Label Secretary, Local 121, D.C., Cincinnati) 1914-17, Discussion of the need for "papers in as many languages as is being spoken in our organization;" significant letter (12/02/14) from Schlossberg describing the H. Sonneborn & Co. lockout. (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - Manenin, Florence (Local 38, Dayton, Ohio) 1914 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Manion, E.J. (Order of Railway Telegraphers) 1925 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Margales, Joseph (Secretary-Treasurer) Joint Board of Montreal) 1917-18 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Margone, Joseph (Montreal Joint Board) 1917, Gardner shop workers refuse to work piece work. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Marcovitz, Lazarus (Manager, Boston Joint Board) 1915 (Box 13, Folder 8-9)
  - Marcovitz, Lazarus, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Marcovitz, Lazarus, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
  - Marcovitz, Lazarus, 1918, Organizing Montreal workers. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Marcovitz, Lazarus, 1920-23 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Marimpietri, Joseph (President, Local 39, Chicago) 1914-25, Edward Anderson (Business Manager, Local 61) possible charge of embezzlement; strategy in Louisville. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Marleib, J. (Secretary, Local 18, Buffalo) 1918 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - McDevitt, E.P. (Steubenville Typographical Union) 1920 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - McNab, Mary (Business Agent, United Tailors of Hamilton, Ontario) 1917-18, States that 95% of gentile cutters are "prejudiced against Bro. Shapiro for different reasons." Describes the Dundas strike as "really a woman's strike." Mary McNab's resignation. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Meccia, Marco (Cincinnati Joint Board) 1925 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Mellon, Joseph (attorney) 1915 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Miller, S. (Toronto Joint Board) 1918-25 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Milne, Bailey (Trade Union Congress, Great Britain) 1924 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Monat, Peter (New York Joint Board) 1918 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Mooney, Tom, 1918 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Morelli, Thomas (Boston Joint Board) 1918 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Morris, Alice (Local 150, Boston) 1917 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Morrison, Frank (Secretary, American Federation of Labor) 1919 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Moses, Jacob (attorney, Baltimore, MD) 1919 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Muste, A.J. (Amalgamated Textile Workers) 1919-20 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Nearing, Scott, 1923-25 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Nemetzsky, I. (Secretary, Local 12, New York City) 1919, Graft in children's clothing. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - New Republic, 1915, "terms of the settlement made in the Chicago Clothing Workers strike." (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - New York American, 1915, Statement upon the sinking of the Lusitania. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Novick, Dora (Secretary, United Tailors of Cleveland) 1916-18 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - O'Brien and Powell (ACWA attorneys, Rochester) 1919-20, Joseph Michaels et al v. Sidney Hillman et al. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Oran, Jennie (Local 137, Scranton) 1920 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Palenti, George (Rochester Brotherhood of Tailors) 1917 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Pankin, Jennie (Chicago organizer) 1915 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Paskevicia, V. (Lithuanian Branch, ACWA) 1920 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Perlstein, M. (ILGWU) 1916 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Pessin, Sam (St. Louis, Journeymen Tailors Union) 1920 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Plettl, M. (Berlin) 1925, letter written in German. (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Plotkin, A. (Manager, Los Angeles Joint Board) 1923 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Porter, Eugene (New York State Dept. of Markets) 1920 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Potofsky, Jacob, 1914-15, Police brutality against women strikers; striker killed by a strike breaker. (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Potofsky, Jacob, 1916, Internal dissension in Chicago and New York. (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Potofsky, Jacob, 1917-27, Organizing Philadelphia; report on growth of organization. (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Pound, J. (D.C.#3, Baltimore) 1916 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Powdermaker, Hortense (Rochester Joint Board) 1925 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Projansky, William J. (Local 16) 1914 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Provisional Committee of Relief, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Pruseika, L. (Lithuanian Women's Progressive Alliance) 1925 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Rabkin, E. (Montreal Joint Board) 1914-20, Schlossberg's discussions of organizing drives in Boston, Montreal and other cities in northeast Canada and United States. (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Ramaglia, Anthony, 1918 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Rankin, Mildred (Baltimore Joint Board) 1920 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Rappaport, Harris L. (Organizer, Canada) 1914 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Reinisch, B. (Organizer, Local 266, San Francisco) 1925, Charge that Reinisch misused Local funds refuted. (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Rice, Robert (U.S. Employment Service) 1919, Issue of allegations that the U.S. Employment Service is furnishing strike breakers. (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Ripley, William Z. (U.S. War Dept., Office of Quartermaster General) 1918 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Rishikoff, B. (Secretary-Treasurer, Joint Board of Montreal) 1917, Organizing Quebec City. (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Rissman, Sidney (Chicago, Clothing Cutters and Trimmers Association) 1917-25 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Roewer, George (ACWA attorney, N.Y.C.) 1914, Significant correspondence relating to the Leopold-Morse Co. strike. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Roman, N. (Jewish Forward) 1915 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Rosen, Charles (Local 14, Rochester, N.Y.) 1925 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Rosen, J. (Secretary-Treasurer, Toronto Brotherhood of Tailors) 1917 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Rosenberg, V. (Organizer, United Tailors of Hamilton, Ontario) 1916 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Rosenberger, Max (Cleveland clothing worker) 1918 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Rosenblatt, Joseph (secretary, Shirt and Boys' Waist Workers and Ironers' Union) 1918 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Rosenbloom, H.D. (Toronto Joint Board) 1918-25, Agreement with the W.R. Johnston Co. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Rosenblum, Frank (Chicago Joint Board) 1914-16, May, Includes discussion of union activities in Chicago, Milwaukee, Rochester, New York, Philadelphia and Boston. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Rosenblum, Frank, 1916, June-December (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Rosenblum, Frank, 1917, January-March (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Rosenblum, Frank, 1917, April-June (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Rosenblum, Frank, 1917, July-August (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Rosenblum, Frank, 1917, September-1925, October (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Rotonde, John (Local 202, Rochester, N.Y.) 1925 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Rudnick, Charles (Organizer, Chicago) 1917 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Rudolph, Samuel, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Rudow, Samuel (Manager, Philadelphia Joint Board) 1923-25 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - St. Louis Labor, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Salutsky, J.B. (J.B.S. Hardman) 1925 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Sandler, M. (Toronto clothing worker) 1918 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Savonovsky, Abraham (St. Louis clothing worker) 1918 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Sax, Samuel (Chicago Joint Board) 1914 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Sayvetz, J. (Ladies Waist Workers Union) 1915 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Schapiro, I. (Organizer, Buffalo, Cleveland, Hamilton, Ontario) 1916-18 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Schecter, William (Cutters and Trimmers of Montreal) 1914 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Schiff, Jacob (Attorney, American Men's & Boy's Clothing Manufacturers' Association) 1918-19 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Schlesinger, Benjamin (ILGWU) 1920 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Schlossberg, Bess, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 13a)
  - Schneid, Hyman (Chicago organizer) 1916-17 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Schulman, Herman (Local 40, N.Y.C.) 1917 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Sclare, M. (Assistant Secretary, Tailors and Garment Workers Union, Leeds, England) 1925 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Scott, David (Local 120, Louisville, Kentucky) 1918 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Seckular, S. (Secretary, Local 112, Cleveland) 1917 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Sharfatz, S. (Clothing Worker, Local 210, Hamilton, Ontario) 1920 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Sharpat, S. (Local 210, Hamilton, Ontario) 1917 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Shatz, Ida (United Tailors of Cleveland) 1918 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Shear, B. (Local 86, Pittsburgh) 1920 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Shepherd, Anna (Secretary, Local 120, Louisville, Kentucky) 1918-20 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Sher, H. (Pants Makers Union of Worcester, Mass,) 1917-18 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Shiplacoff, Abraham, 1916-18 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Shoenfeld, Meyer (Clothing Trades Labor Adjustment and Information Bureau) 1915 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Siegel, Isaac (Congressmen, N.Y.C.) 1916 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Sillins, Max (Journeymen Tailors Union of Chicago) 1918 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Silverman, Samuel (Manager, Philadelphia Joint Board) 1914-19 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Sindler, Harry (Baltimore Clothing Workers) 1920 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Sinkus, P. (Pants Makers Union of Baltimore) 1915, Organizing Lithuanian workers. (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Sisber, Jack (Toronto Joint Board) 1918 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Skala, Stephen (Slovak Coat Makers Union of Chicago) 1915-18, Report on the Gaylord Stores Co. strike. (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Skinner, Mary (Buffalo clothing worker) 1923 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Skolnick, S. (Secretary, Local 15, Baltimore) 1917 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Slade, Helen, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Slovin, A.R. (Secretary, Pants Makers Union of Worcester, Mass.) 1917 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Smith, Alfred (Governor of N.Y.) 1920, Fearen bills and Lusk bills. (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Smith, Luther E., 1925 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Smoloff, H. (Chairman, Local 207, Woodbine, N.J.) 1918 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Smulewitz, Harry (United Tailors of Cleveland) 1915, Support for Chicago strikers. (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Snyder, J. (Local 210, Hamilton, Ontario) 1917, Milos Vojnovich Defense Fund. (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Socialist Labor Party (Arnold Paterson) 1925 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Solomon, D. (Manager, Cleveland Joint Board) (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Sonneborn, Siegmund, 1917-18 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Spitz, J. (Cleveland Joint Board) 1919-20 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Srulemitz, Morris (Local 151, Milwaukee) 1917, "Working conditions formulated by the employees of D. Adler & Son." (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Stahley, George (Rochester Brotherhood of Tailors) 1917 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Starr, Ellen Gates (Hull House) 1916 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Stephans, William D. (Governor of California) 1918, The Mooney case. (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Steinhardt, David, 1918 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Stern, Edwin (Organizer, St. Louis) 1915 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Stone, N.J. (Hickey Freeman) 1920 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Strabel, Gustav (Rochester Joint Board) 1920-25 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Strauss, E. (Secretary, Local 15, Baltimore) 1916 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Strom, L. (Toronto Joint Board) 1923-25 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Suder, George (Secretary, Local 121, Cincinnati) 1914-16 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Sweeney, Thomas (Journeymen Tailors Union) 1915-20 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Sykes, Abe (Basters Union of Baltimore) 1914 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Taback (Comrade) 1918, Re The Palestine Congress Committee. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Tailors and Garment Workers Union (London) 1925, Establishing a correspondence with the ACWA. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Tailors, United Brotherhood of, 1915 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Tatelman, N. (Organizer, Worcester, Mass.) 1918 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Taylor, George N., 1924, Investing in the Russian-American Industrial Corporation (RAIC). (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Tilla, K. (Local 138, Philadelphia) 1925 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Tippett, T., 1925 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Tovey, Charles (Manager, Toronto Joint Board) 1920 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Trade Union Committee to Organize the Purcell Meeting, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Trade Union Unity, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Truin, Thomas (Organizer, Baltimore) 1923 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Tumulty, J.P. (Secretary to President Woodrow Wilson) 1917 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Turk, H. (Secretary, Local 241, Baltimore) 1915-17 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Vaile, Adeline (Open Forum Speakers Bureau) 1923 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Valenti, George (Rochester Brotherhood of Tailors) 1917 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Van Der Heeg (Comrade) 1920 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Vinett, F.W. (Joint Board of Toronto) 1918 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Vladeck, B. (Jewish Daily Forward) 1914 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Volpe, Thomas, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Wagner, Anna (Vest Makers Union) 1914 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - War Dept. Administrator of Labor Standards, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Webman, J. (Organizer, Cleveland) 1918 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Weinstein, M. (Manager, N.Y. Clothing Cutters & Trimmers Union) 1923 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Weisman, J. (Cleveland Joint Board) 1916 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Weiss, Louis (Chicago Cutters) 1918 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Wertheimer, N. (Buffalo Joint Board) 1923 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - White, John, (Comrade) 1916 (Box 17, Folder 31)